# Jayme Rayne Reyna

# jayme.reyna@utexas.edu 512-599-3646

#### **PROFILE**

Pre-Med student at The University of Texas at Austin. Has previous experience as a Certified Nurse Aide, Medical Scribe in Urgent Care setting, as well as over 100 hours performing clinical rotations. Hard-working, quick learner, and extremely adaptable.

### **EXPERIENCE**

Cashier, H-E-B; Austin, Texas — 2018-2019

Gained valuable hands-on experience in a customer service setting.

Medical Scribe, NextCare Urgent Care; Austin, Texas — 2017-2018

Gained valuable hands-on experience within an Urgent Care setting scribing and learning from several medical professionals.

Certified Nurse Aide, Retama Nursing Home; Alice, Texas — 2014-2015

Gained valuable hands-on experience within the nursing home performing and perfecting common Nurse Aide skills.

Health Science Technology Clinical Rotations, Christus Spohn Hospital; Alice, Texas — 2014-2015

Became accustomed to the various departments within a hospital, as well as became familiar with common medical terminology and procedures.

#### **EDUCATION**

The University of Texas at Austin, Austin, Texas — BSA Biology, Pre-Medicine, Class of 2021

Alice High School, Alice, Texas — Class of 2016

## **SKILLS**

- Statistical software: R
- Programming Language: Python